Contact

bridget.beason@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ bridget-beason-rn-bsn-ccrncsc-3b3285145 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Ccrn

Basic Life Support (BLS)
Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Bridget Beason, RN,BSN, CCRN-CSC

RN,CCRN,CSC at Texoma Medical Center
Dallas/Fort Worth Area

Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Critical Care, MICU, TNCC, Basic Life Support (BLS), and Cardiac Intensive Care. Strong healthcare services professional with a Rn focused in Nursing Education from Butler Community College. Extremely driven in life!! Never gives up on anything!

Experience

Texoma Medical Center RN,CCRN,CSC October 2019 - Present (8 months) Denison, Texas

Paris Regional Medical Center
7 years 5 months

CCRN,CSC

August 2018 - October 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Paris, Texas

CCRN

June 2012 - October 2019 (7 years 5 months)
Paris, texas

NPC FITNESS LTD.

NPC FITNESS COMPETITOR

April 2016 - October 2019 (3 years 7 months)

Rainbow Home Health Registered Nurse March 2017 - July 2017 (5 months) Idabel, Oklahoma

Branch Director

McConnel AirForce Base Civil Servant January 2010 - August 2011 (1 year 8 months) Wichita, Kansas

LPN

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Master's in Science of Nursing Family Nurse Practioner, Nursing

Science · (2018 - 2020)

Butler Community College Rn, Nursing Education · (2010 - 2011)